Now, I'd like to go to an Akanta Idol main project like that.
I'm sorry to ask you to do this too, Mr. Usuki.
Can I ask this to Cute?
I understand. Leave it to me.
I'll go!
My three elements!
Yay!
You're as cute as you can be!
Yes, as much as I can.
Thank you!
I have chosen!
Now then, may I have your three main elements?
Okay, I'll do that. Here are my 3 main elements!
Ta-da!
Let's start with number one!
The first is ramen, the second is stoicism, and the third is talkativeness.
I see!
Ramen is my favorite food!
Ehhhh...
I really like it, like 3 times a week.
That's a lot!
If I include cup ramen in my diet.
I think it's more like 5 a week.
I see.
Sometimes I eat it twice a day.
That's a lot!
That's right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
By the way, what is the best ramen in Sendai?
There's a ramen shop called "Opechan" that has black mar oil in it.
Oppeshan!
I've been going there since I was in junior high school.
They are also a sponsor of my radio show.
We've even collaborated with them on some ramen dishes.
Is that so?
That's right.
What's that? Not a group? A collaboration as an individual?
No, it's just that I like this Mr. Opechian.
So it's more of an interview.
Well, yes...
I went there for a radio show, and that's when I got the chance.
I became a sponsor of the group.
Oh, you're the one who started it all, aren't you?
I got the job.
That's good.
No, it's good.
I'll leave it to you to imitate me.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're right, I'm in the groove.
Yes, it is.
It's got Tork's logo on it.
That's right.
What's the appeal of ramen?
What? But I think it's fast, cheap, and good.
I see.
Yes, partly because I really like the taste.
But they come out quickly.
And it's easy to go alone.
I see.
It's pretty much a counter.
There are a lot of businessmen around.
but they all come alone.
So I feel less intimidated than when I go to a family restaurant.
I'm not afraid of going alone.
That's why I go alone.
I'm quite impatient.
I'm not the slow course type.
I think I'm an impatient type.
That's why I like conveyor-belt sushi.
It's fast.
I can take whatever I want, eat it, and go home.
I like fast places like that.
Good bye.
Delicious!
Yakanta Idol
Kazumi, if I could, I'd like to be your aunt.
Mayumi
Keisuke
Tempura Hiroshi
Courtesy of
Thank you very much!